(Leonard:)-Come on. It's okay.
-No, it's not okay!
(Penny:)Look at me, okay? I took a temp job
as a waitress forever ago,
(Penny:)and I'm still doing it.
I can't quit, because guess what?
(Penny:)I can't do anything else.
(Penny:)And I finally get my big break,
and it goes away! I'm such a mess.
(Leonard:)-No, you're not.
-Really?
'Cause this morning at Starbucks,
(Penny:)a pair of old underwear
fell out cf my pant leg!
(Penny:)And it wasn't the only
one in there.
(Leonard:)Okay, listen to me,
this is just a minor setback.
(Penny:)No, it's not, okay? I've been out
here for, like, ten years!
-I've nothing to show for it!
-Well, you have me.
(Penny:)You're right.
(Penny:)I do have you.
Mmm.
(Penny:)Let's get married.
(Leonard:)What?
Whoo.
(Penny:)Leonard Hofstadter,
will you marry me?